[
    {
        "front": "ぼく",
        "back": "I (by boys)",
        "chapter": "N4 C15"
    },
    {
        "front": "きみ",
        "back": "you (by boys)",
        "chapter": "N4 C15"
    },
    {
        "front": "ハンバーグ",
        "back": "hamburger",
        "chapter": "N4 C15"
    },
    {
        "front": "スパケッティ",
        "back": "spaghetti",
        "chapter": "N4 C15"
    },
    {
        "front": "うかがう",
        "back": "to ask",
        "chapter": "N4 C15"
    },
    {
        "front": "べつべつ（に）",
        "back": "separately",
        "chapter": "N4 C15"
    },
    {
        "front": "べつ",
        "back": "separate; different",
        "chapter": "N4 C15"
    },
    {
        "front": "はらう",
        "back": "to pay",
        "chapter": "N4 C15"
    },
    {
        "front": "あじ",
        "back": "taste",
        "chapter": "N4 C15"
    },
    {
        "front": "こい",
        "back": "strong",
        "chapter": "N4 C15"
    },
    {
        "front": "いかがですか",
        "back": "polite version of \"どうですか\"",
        "chapter": "N4 C15"
    }
]